[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the first soap opera broadcast on an American television network?", "correct_answer": "Faraway Hill", "incorrect_answers": ["Halls of Ivy", "Love of Life", "Love of Ivy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sport had Arnold Schwarzenegger practiced before he took up bodybuilding?", "correct_answer": "Soccer", "incorrect_answers": ["Tennis", "Rugby", "Baseball"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This species of great apes with long arms and reddish hair suffer habitat destruction due to logging, mining and forest fires.", "correct_answer": "Orangutan", "incorrect_answers": ["Gorilla", "Baboons", "Chimpanzee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a fast-spinning neutron star that emits pulses of radio waves called?", "correct_answer": "Pulsar", "incorrect_answers": ["Millisecondar", "White Dwarf", "Magnetar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What continent does the large Griffon Vulture inhabit?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "Europe", "Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Since its separation from the Roman Catholic church in 1534, this branch of Christianity acts as a mother branch of the worldwide Anglican Communion.", "correct_answer": "Church of  England", "incorrect_answers": ["Lutheranism", "Sufism", "Calvinism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kagiso Kuypers portrays Hounsous son in the movie Blood Diamond. What does he become?", "correct_answer": "A very good soldier", "incorrect_answers": ["A very good medic for the S.L.R.F.", "A very good slave for the S.L.R.F.", "A very good diamond miner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What process does the edible seaweed called Wakame accelerate according to studies?", "correct_answer": "Burning of fat", "incorrect_answers": ["Healing of wounds", "Cell growth", "Delivery of the baby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Princess Protection Program, Rosie has to count worms.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was Kevin Bacon born?", "correct_answer": "July 8th 1958", "incorrect_answers": ["May 8th 1958", "April 8th 1960", "April 8th 1959"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why do Joe and Jerry disguise themselves as women in the 1959 comedy movie Some Like It Hot?", "correct_answer": "Because they have witnessed a murder", "incorrect_answers": ["Because they have perpetrated a crime", "Because they want to get closer to girls", "Because they like wearing stockings and wigs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are reindeer antlers used as a food by humans?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}]